

# Syauqi Sabili

**Date of birth:** 19/02/1999 | **Place of birth:** Tangerang, Indonesia | **Nationality:** Indonesian |

**Gender:** Male | **Email address:** syaugisabili@gmail.com | **Website:** 

https://syauqisabili.github.io

## **ABOUT ME**

3 years of professional experience in payment software development with a can-do attitude and a passion for lifelong learning. Proficiency with ISO 8583, EMV, and POS applications. Skilled in GUI development using Qt. Currently focusing on backend services using Go.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

01/10/2024 - CURRENT Jakarta, Indonesia

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER PT ELCARIM OPTRONIC INDONESIA**

- Backend services for vessel tracking systems supporting NMEA 0183 and ITU-R M.1371.
- Real-time services for publishing AIS, TTM, and radar video streams (ASTERIX CAT240).

11/10/2021 - 30/09/2024 Jakarta, Indonesia

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER PT PRIMAVISTA SOLUSI (EX WIRECARD ASIA PACIFIC)**

- Terminal Software Management for Ingenico POS (T2, T+, Tetra) using C/C++.
- Teller applications based on requirements.
- Buy now pay later (ATOME, KREDIVO, INDODANA) and QRIS (ShopeePay, OVO) POS applications.
- Maintainer for Ingenico and Linux-based payment applications.

01/02/2021 - 01/07/2021 Bandung, Indonesia

## **ENGINEER INTERN (REMOTE)** TELKOM INDONESIA

- Served in a research team that explored Virtual Evolved Packet Core, NextEPC.
- Cloud Native Technology based on telecom requirements.
- Set up and optimize infrastructure, tools, and configurations for proof of concept (POC).

## EDUCATION AND TRAINING

08/2017 - 08/2021 Surabaya, Indonesia

**BACHELOR DEGREE** Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember

Address 60111, Surabaya, Indonesia | Field of study Computer Engineering | Final grade 3.54 |

**Thesis** Face Verification Using Deep Metric Learning on Face Data with Large Age Disparity

## NETWORKS AND MEMBERSHIPS

01/2018 - 10/2020 Surabaya, Indonesia

## **Embedded Software Engineer - ITS Quadruped Robot Research Club**

- Involved in the development of gait planning to determine the motion trajectory and posture of legs.
- Designed and developed GUI for robot monitoring system using Qt.
- Designed and developed a slave microcontroller, ATmega16 to acquire data sensors.
- Responsible for the main code of master microcontroller, STM32F4 Discovery.